

# Pezhman Ghavami

Front-End Engineer

☑ mail@pezhmanghavami.com

♠ pezhmanghavami.com

github.com/pezhmanghavami

## **Abut Me**

Over the past four years, I co-founded Rayabot and started my journey as a developer; During this time, I took various ideas into production and solving such a wide variety of problems helped me better understand different parts of an applications stack. Through these experiences, I found a passion for Front-End engineering and shifted my skills toward it!

# **Experience**

# Co-Founder and Full-Stack Developer - Rayabot 다

May 2017- February 2022

2019-2021

Worked with a team of developers and designers to build a Software as a Service product which included:

- A user control panel for managing subscriptions
- An admin control panel to manage users and the instances of our automated trading software
- Product performance data visualization in the admin panel
- An SSE server for broadcasting our trading software's server instance events to the clients
- A client in the cTrader platform as a cBot
- A GUI made using electron to act as a bridge client for MetaTrader React • Redux-Toolkit • React Router • Sass • Styled Components • D3.js • Electron • Express.js • PostgreSQL • Redis • JavaScript • C# • cAlgo • MQL5

#### 2019

Made an internal REST API for authenticating and managing our various trading software.

Express.js • JavaScript

#### 2018

Made a WordPress e-commerce website.

WordPress

#### 2017-2022

Closely collaborated with the trading team to turn their strategies into indicators and automated trading solutions in the cAlgo platform. cAlgo • C#

....

2017-2022

Made several telegram bots for broadcasting indicator signals, delivering trade notifications, and monitoring different trading software statuses.

Node.js • Prisma • SQLite • JavaScript • TypeScript

## **Skills**

## **Programming Languages**

JavaScript (ES6), TypeScript, HTML, CSS/Sass

#### **Libraries & Frameworks**

React.js, Next.js, Redux Toolkit, React Router, Prisma, SWR, React Query, Tailwindcss, Styled Components, Zustand, D3.js, Socket.io, ws, Jest, Cypress, tRPC, Express.js, Node.js

## **Tools & Platforms**

Git, Webpack, Vite, Netliy, Firebase, Vercel, Docker, Github Actions

# **Projects**

## Clothing Shop ☑

A prototype e-commerce website built with Next.js, React, Tailwindcss, SWR, Prisma and TypeScript

# Chat App ☑

A prototype chat application built using the PERN stack, Tailwindcss, react-router, SWR, Prisma, Socket.io and TypeScript

## Sorting Visualizer <a>□</a>

A web app to visualize different sorting algorithms built using React and TypeScript

# **Education**

# **Azad University - Shiraz**

Sep 2016 - Jun 2020

Information Technology